trafficbonus.com 2019-06-29

# Traffic Bonus Member's Area

Who we are

Ad Labs Inc. (“Ad Labs,” “we,” “us”) is a Corporation of Canada and owns and controls the website Trafficbonus.com. Your privacy is very important to us, and this privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give us when you use this website or our services. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website or our services, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Privacy Policy Updates

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

Data Security

Data security is of the utmost importance to us and we are committed to ensuring the information we collect from you is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online and offline. 

What personal data we collect and why we collect it

Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment. 

Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website. 

Contact forms

When visitors submit comments via the contact forms on the site we collect the data shown in the form in order to respond to your request, and also to help spam detection. 

Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer or other devices when you visit a website. They are very widely used in order to make websites function properly, or more efficiently, as well as provide information to the owners of the site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any personal information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google Advertising Settings Page](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated) If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year. If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed. If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day. By using our website, you imply consent to the use of cookies. However, if you do not consent to the use of cookies, please ensure that your browser or computer/device is set to reject or prompt before accepting third-party cookies. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

Analytics

Information that you provide to us when completing a form on our website, filling out a questionnaire, placing an order, subscribing to email or mailing lists, participating in surveys, and when contacting us both on and offline including: 

  * Name, contact information (such as phone and email), address.
  * Information automatically received by us when you use the website, access our marketing information, or contact us by email or phone. We also use software tools such as Google Analytics to measure and collect session information, length of visits to certain pages, and help us understand how visitors use our website. This information may include IP addresses, browser type and version, operating system, device, and service provider, and more.If you wish not to have send information about your website visit to Google Analytics, download and install the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) for your current web browser. The Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on does not prevent information from being sent to our website or to other web analytics services.

Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, audio, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website. 

Who we share your data with

By using our website, you imply consent to the use of cookies. However, if you do not consent to the use of cookies, please ensure that your browser or computer/device is set to reject or prompt before accepting third party cookies. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

Who Else May See Your Data

Please be aware that due to the nature of our business and of the internet, information and data you provide may be transferred outside the country where it is submitted to us. If you are submitting information or data from a country within the European Economic Area (EEA) it is possible that it may be transferred outside the EEA, where data privacy regulations may differ from within the EEA. 

Controlling Your Personal Information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. In the event of a sale or acquisition of all or a portion of our assets, we may be required to transfer business assets, including information that we have collected. We will notify you by email and/or place a notice on our website. We may disclose your information if required to do so pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants, and orders, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we retain the right to use, disclose and/or share your information to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person whether or not there is a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure. You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information, and/or update and request details of any personal information which we hold about you, by contacting us via our website or at support [at] hacktheentrepreneur [dot] com. 

Third Party Service Providers

We use a third-party online payment gateway provider to process credit card payments. You will be providing credit or debit card information directly to the provider and not to us. Information that you supply to the provider in making a payment is not within our control and is subject to its own terms and policies. We may also use other third-party service providers to help us operate our business and our website, or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. 

Third Party Websites

Our website may contain links to the sites and services of partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors, and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by sites linked to or from our website. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy and other policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites linked to our website, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies. We cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting third-party sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy policy. 

How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information. 

What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. 

Applicable Law and Choice of Forum

This privacy policy is governed by the laws of the Province of Ontario, Canada. All matters arising out of these terms shall be resolved exclusively by the provincial and federal courts located in Toronto, Ontario. For this purpose, each party consents to personal jurisdiction in such provincial or federal court and waives any right to dismiss or transfer such action or proceeding because of the inconvenience of the forum. Nothing in this section shall prevent enforcement in another forum of any judgment obtained in a court identified in this paragraph. 

Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this website, you accept this privacy policy. By providing your personal data, you consent to the use, processing, storing, transferring and disclosing of your information and data referred to in this policy statement for the purposes set out in this privacy policy statement. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

_This document was last updated on May 24, 2018_
